I was falling asleep while sitting down.  Suddenly the phone rang.
Hello, who is this?  Parcel.  Who throws Oma like this
?  But I didn't order any parcel.
What's in it?  I ripped it apart.
Oma saw a food in the box.  I'm
afraid to open the box.  The phone rang again.   The
ItSrima page sent me a gift.
Then the box can be opened.
I opened the box.  I went to God.
[Loud laughter] Itsurima Apu
sent me a beautiful watch.  I read the watch in my hand.  I feel like
Benten.  It's
hero time.  Oh my, I've become the poor man's
Hulkman.  [Loud laughter] It's
Rima's page only has 200 followers.  I changed the time on my watch and
went to the future.  Oh my goodness, you've gone
viral even more than me.
[Loud laughter] Like if you like Hulk.
Subscribe if you like Spiderman.